<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Copa America 2021 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Copa America 2021 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 11:30:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-13/</guid>
      <description>Peru v Paraguay Goals Gomez(PAR) 11&amp;rsquo; Gomez(OG) 21&#39;
Lapadula(PER) 40&amp;rsquo;
Alonso(PAR) 54&amp;rsquo;
Yotun(PER) 80&#39;
Avalos (PER) 90&amp;rsquo;
Penalties Romero (0-1)
Lapadula (1-1)
Alonso (1-2)
Yotun (2-2)
Martinez (2-2)
Ormeno (2-2)
Samudio (2-2)
Tapia (3-2)
Da Motta (3-3)
Cueva (3-3)
Espinola (3-3)
Trauco (4-3)
A very thrilling game and Peru almost threw it all away when Carrilo got sent off for a second yellow and Paraguay equalised before full time to take it to penalties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-10/</guid>
      <description>Uruguay v Paraguay Goals Cavani (P) 21&amp;rsquo;
Seems to be a drab game overall. Uruguay were threatening but not clinical enough. A penalty which was given by VAR was put in by Cavani. This means they are through and avoid Brazil in the Quarters.
Bolivia v Argentina Goals Gomez 6&#39;
Messi (P) 33&#39;
Messi 42&amp;rsquo;
Saavedra 60&amp;rsquo;
Martinez 65&amp;rsquo;
Great game from Messi who is now Argentina&amp;rsquo;s all time leader in appearances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-9/</guid>
      <description>Brazil v Ecuador Goals Militao 37&#39;
Mena 53&#39;
Brazil did the obvious since they were already qualified and rotated the squad. Eder Militao scored the opener with a great header. Mena later equalised later for the away team to equalise. Brazil go through as group toppers and Ecuador go through due to the next result.
Venezuela v Peru Goals Carrilo 48&amp;rsquo;
Peru were largely dominant in this game but weren&amp;rsquo;t clinical enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-8/</guid>
      <description>Bolivia v Uruguay Goals Quinteros(OG) 40&#39;
Cavani 79&amp;rsquo;
Finally Uruguay have a win and are through as well to the quarter finals. Bolivia had an early chance but missed it. Later finally, Uruguay managed to score when a cross was put into their own net by Quinteros who was trying to prevent the ball reaching Cavani. Later Cavani made it 2 when a low cross was met by him and he scored easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-7/</guid>
      <description>Ecuador v Peru Goals Tapia (OG) 23&#39;
Preciado 48&#39;
Lapadula 49&#39;
Carrillo 54&amp;rsquo;
Ecuador were very poor defensively. After getting the lead from and own goal and a great goal. They managed to concede very quickly in the second half thanks to a brilliant performance from Lapadula(1 goal and assist) who actually changed nations from Italy.
Brazil v Colombia Goals Diaz 10&amp;rsquo;
Firmino 78&#39;
Casemiro 90&#39;+10
Yes you are reading that right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-6/</guid>
      <description>Uruguay v Chile Goals Vargas 26&#39;
Vidal(OG) 66&#39;
An equal game, but you could say Uruguay had more chances and could&amp;rsquo;ve been more clinical. A few chances went over. Chile however took the lead when Vargas slotted it in from a tight angle. Uruguay equalised from Luis Suarez but the last touch was from Vidal so it went down as an own goal. Uruguay are yet to win in this tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-5/</guid>
      <description>Venezuela v Ecuador Goals (ECU)Preciado 39&amp;rsquo;
(VEN)Castillo 51&amp;rsquo;
(ECU)Plata 71&amp;rsquo;
(VEN)Hernandez 91&amp;rsquo;
An entertaining match which was helped with the lack of marking from Ecuador which made the goals from Venezuela too easy. This means both of these teams are at the bottom of the group with Ecuador having their next game being against Peru.
Colombia v Peru Goals (PER)Pena 17&#39;
(COL)Borja(P) 53&#39;
(PER)Mina(OG) 64&#39;
A weird own goal from Yerry Mina meant Peru walked away from this with all 3 points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-4/</guid>
      <description>Chile v Bolivia Goals Brereton 10&amp;rsquo;
An early goal from Brereton secured the deal for Chile. Chile missed a few decent chances and the Bolivia keeper was on fire. Bolivia were okayish going forward. Had a few chances but none were absolute clear cut chances as Bravo was mostly untroubled.
Argentina v Uruguay Goals Guido Rodríguez 13&amp;rsquo;
A win finally from Argentina. A lot of chances fell for both sides but Argentina took the lead from a brilliant cross from Messi and Rodriguez finished things off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Colombia v Venezuela A dull bland game overall. Chances were few and far between for both sides with Colombia getting more of them than Venezuela. Respectable point for them given they were slaughtered by Brazil.
Brazil v Peru Goals Alex Sandro 12&#39;
Neymar 68&#39;
Everton 89&#39;
Richarlison 90&#39;+3
A brilliant performance from the &amp;ldquo;hosts&amp;rdquo; as they have almost sealed their passage to the next round. Neymar is actually 9 short of Pele&amp;rsquo;s record now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Argentina v Chile Goals Messi 33&#39;
Vargas 57&#39;
An even match. Messi got underway with an amazing free kick past Bravo(Just Messi things) The equaliser was classic Argentina which was annoying. Vidal took a penalty which was tipped to the crossbar but Vargas scored on the rebound.
Paraguay v Bolivia Goals Saavedra(P) 10&#39;
Romero 62&#39;
Romero 65&#39;
Romero 80&#39;
Although Bolivia scored the first goal with a pen and went into half-time in the lead, the red card changed everything and immediately Paraguay attacked hard and scored 3 simple goals making the numerical advantage count.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 12:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021/posts/day-1/</guid>
      <description>Brazil v Venezuela Goals Marquinhos 23&#39;
Neymar(P) 64&#39;
Gabriel Barbosa 89&#39;
A very dominant display from the new hosts. Should&amp;rsquo;ve been at least 4 or 5 given the types of chances they got. Marquinhos scored the first one from the corner with a brilliant. Neymar then scored a pen and could&amp;rsquo;ve had a hat trick at the very least. Finally he assisted Gabigol after rounding the keeper.
Colombia v Ecuador Goals E.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>